acronymsandslang.com 2016-10-14

# Privacy Policy

Acronymsandslang.com respects the privacy of visitors to its Web site.

We want you to feel secure using our web site. The guidelines below explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how we protect the privacy of visitors to Acronymsandslang.com. 

### Consent to this Privacy Policy

By providing us with Personal Information, you signify that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted here. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not provide any Personal Information. If you choose not to provide Personal Information, you may not be able to take certain actions, like becoming an editor, access particular areas of the web site, posting comments to our Blog, or send us e-mail.

### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to administer our Web site ant to Protect our website from any kinds of activity that breaks the terms of use of this site.

### Cookies

We use cookies and software logs to monitor the use of Acronymsandslang.com and to gather non-personal information about visitors to the site. Cookies are small files that Acronymsandslang transfers to the hard drives of visitors for record-keeping purposes. These monitoring systems allow us to track general information about our visitors, such as the type of browsers (for example, Firefox or Internet Explorer), the operating systems (for instance, Windows or Macintosh), or the Internet providers (for instance, Comcast) they use. This information is used for statistical and market research purposes to tailor content to usage patterns and to provide services requested by our customers. To delete these cookies, please see your browser's privacy settings.

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. AcronymsAndSlang.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those third-party Web sites.

### Security

Any personally identifiable information collected through this site is stored on limited-access servers. We have security measures to protect these servers and the information they store.

### Continuing Agreement

Acronymsandslang.com may change or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this posting. Please review this Privacy Policy each time you visit this web site in order to be aware of the most current terms regarding your use of this web site. Your use of this web site reaffirms your continuing agreement to the most current Privacy Policy. 

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via our: Feedback Form
